<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on pabes.me</title>
    <link>https://pabes.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on pabes.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pabes.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills for your SOAR team to succeed</title>
      <link>https://pabes.me/blog/skillsets-for-sustainable-playbook-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pabes.me/blog/skillsets-for-sustainable-playbook-development/</guid>
      <description>Many Security Operation Centres will assume that playbook development could (or should) solely be completed by security analysts. While it is difficult to narrow down exactly where this comes from; I suspect it comes from vendor&amp;rsquo;s marketing the ease of use of their solutions and the inclusion of WYSIWYG and drag and drop editors.
Whilst it is possible for security analysts to create functioning instances of playbooks many SOCs will encounter difficulties scaling this approach and thus hindering the value realisation of the products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bibliography of career thoughts</title>
      <link>https://pabes.me/blog/career-advice-bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pabes.me/blog/career-advice-bibliography/</guid>
      <description>An assortment of career-related posts that have been challenging or thought provoking in one way or another. Many of these posts are a bit whack but may help you think critically about your career.
   You are not an employee, you are a business.
It&amp;rsquo;s not personal; it&amp;rsquo;s business.
  How to waste your career, one comfortable year at a time
Apoorva (apoorvagovind) provides a framework for evaluating when we are being complacent and the realisation of the true cost of this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smashing Your SANS Course</title>
      <link>https://pabes.me/blog/smashing-your-sans-giac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pabes.me/blog/smashing-your-sans-giac/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this post, you likely know of the SANS course and associated GIAC certification. You&amp;rsquo;re likely about to sit your course and/or exam and are looking for some tips and tricks to maximise the amount of value you get out of this eye-wateringly expensive course. This post is an overview of the tips and tricks that I have for smashing your SANS GIAC experience that I didn&amp;rsquo;t really read in other places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>